Guide to the Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records, 1958-2000.
Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records
- Series IV Projects
  - XXXX
    - Technical Files
      - Procedures
        - #20063 El Rail & Rack Gear Alignment, Original File Number 30.O (Box 71, Folder 10)
        - #20064 - AZ Trolley Work Plan, Original File Number 30.P (Box 71, Folder 11)
        - #20065 Dome Assembly/Instal Plan, Original File Number 30.Q (Box 71, Folder 12)
        - #20066 Phase 3, Feedarm Work Plan, Original File Number 30.R (Box 71, Folder 13)
        - #20067 Phase 2a, Feedarm Work Plan, Original File Number 30.S (Box 71, Folder 14)
        - #20068 - Masts & Booms, Original File Number 30.T (Box 71, Folder 15)
        - #20069 Phase 2b, Work Plan, Original File Number 30.U (Box 71, Folder 16)
        - #20070 - Bolt Tightening, Original File Number 30.V (Box 71, Folder 17)
        - #20071 Bolt Instal/Tightening, Original File Number 30.W (Box 71, Folder 18)
        - #29005 Dome Installation Plan, Original File Number 30.X (Box 71, Folder 19)
        - Hurricane, Original File Number 30.Y (Box 71, Folder 20)
        - #20098 - Dome Trolley Rig/Cross Beam Replacement, Original File Number 30.AA (Box 71, Folder 21)
        - AO El Rail Survey/Alignment, Original File Number 30.BB (Box 71, Folder 22)
      - Reflectors
        - Secondary Reflectors, Panels RFP, Original File Number 31.A (Box 71, Folder 23)
        - Secondary Reflectors, Panels Proposals, Original File Number 31.B (Box 71, Folder 24)
        - Secondary Reflectors, Panels Correspond., Original File Number 31.C (Box 71, Folder 25)
        - Secondary Reflectors, Subreflector Panels Proposals (Box 71, Folder 26)
        - Secondary Reflectors, Backup Struct RFP, Original File Number 31.D (Box 71, Folder 27)
        - Secondary Reflectors, Backup Struct Prop., Original File Number 31.E (Box 71, Folder 28)
        - Secondary Reflectors, Backup Struct Corp., Original File Number 31.F (Box 71, Folder 29)
        - Secondary Reflectors, Backup Struct Supp, Original File Number 31.G (Box 71, Folder 30)
        - Miscellaneous Reflectors, Original File Number 31.H (Box 71, Folder 31)
        - Tertiary Reflectors, Purchase Order #, Original File Number 31.I (Box 71, Folder 32)
        - Tertiary Reflectors, Proposals, Original File Number 31.J (Box 71, Folder 33)
        - Tertiary Reflectors, Correspondence, Original File Number 31.K (Box 71, Folder 34)
        - Tertiary Reflectors, Design & Assembly, Original File Number 31.L (Box 72, Folder 1)
        - Panel Measurement/Targets 2ndary Tertiary, Original File Number 31.M (Box 72, Folder 2)
        - Tertiary Panel Data, Original File Number 31.N (Box 72, Folder 3)
        - Secondary Reflectors, Panel Data, Original File Number 31.O (Box 72, Folder 4)
        - Panel Damage, Original File Number 31.P (Box 72, Folder 5)
        - Secondary Reflectors, Panel Installation, Original File Number 31.Q (Box 72, Folder 6)
        - Imtec - Theodolite Rental, Original File Number 31.R (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Rotary Floor
        - Rack Gear (Griffin), Original File Number 32.A (Box 72, Folder 8)
        - Rack Gear Sections (MTS), Original File Number 32.B (Box 72, Folder 9)
        - Camroll Race (Finger Lakes Fab), Original File Number 32.C (Box 72, Folder 10)
        - Drive System Pinion, Original File Number 32.D (Box 72, Folder 11)
        - Gear Design & Calcs, Original File Number 32.E (Box 72, Folder 12)
        - Tapped Holes, Original File Number 32.F (Box 72, Folder 13)
        - General, Original File Number 32.G (Box 72, Folder 14)
        - Installation, Original File Number 32.H (Box 72, Folder 15)
        - Todco Panels P.O., Original File Number 32.I (Box 72, Folder 16)
        - Miscellaneous Hardware, Original File Number 32.J (Box 72, Folder 17)
        - Raised Floor (Reynolds) (I-Beams), Original File Number 32.K (Box 72, Folder 18)
        - Drives System Install/Procedure, Original File Number 32.L (Box 72, Folder 19)
        - Alignment, Original File Number 32.M (Box 72, Folder 20)
        - Encoders, Original File Number 32.N (Box 72, Folder 21)
        - Reduction Gear (Engineered Gear Systems), Original File Number 32.O (Box 72, Folder 22)
      - S-Band
        - Heat Exchange & Platform (1), Original File Number 33.A (Box 72, Folder 23)
        - Heat Exchange & Platform (2), Original File Number 33.A (Box 72, Folder 24)
        - Misc. Communication (1), Original File Number 33.B (Box 72, Folder 25)
        - Misc. Communication (2), Original File Number 33.B (Box 72, Folder 26)
        - Diesel Fuel Gas Turb. Gen. Sys RFP, Original File Number 33.E (Box 72, Folder 27)
        - Cornell Univ. Change Orders, Original File Number 33.F (Box 72, Folder 28)
        - 430 Mhz Flex. Wavegd/Mega Indust, Original File Number 33.G (Box 72, Folder 29)
        - Emergency Generators/Syracuse Supp, Original File Number 33.H (Box 72, Folder 30)
        - Expansion Tank Supp/Pipe Support, Original File Number 33.I (Box 72, Folder 31)
        - Receiver Equipment (Digi-Key PO), Original File Number 33.J (Box 72, Folder 32)
        - CEC, Original File Number 34 (Box 72, Folder 33)
      - Soil Testers and Steel Magnaflux Testing
        - Soil Borings, Original File Number 35.A (Box 72, Folder 34)
        - Geotech, Original File Number 35.B (Box 72, Folder 35)
        - Testing Bolts (RSI Com 13), Original File Number 36.A (Box 72, Folder 36)
      - Telescope Drive
        - General, Original File Number 37.A (Box 72, Folder 37)
        - Consultant, Original File Number 37.B (Box 72, Folder 38)
        - GBT (GreenBank Telescope), Original File Number 37.C (Box 72, Folder 39)
        - GBT (GreenBank Telescope), Original File Number 37.C (Box 72, Folder 40)
      - Tie Downs
        - Tiedown B4, Original File Number 38.A (Box 72, Folder 41)
        - Tiedown B12, Original File Number 38.B (Box 72, Folder 42)
        - Tiedown B8, Original File Number 38.C (Box 72, Folder 43)
        - General, Original File Number 38.D (Box 72, Folder 44)
        - Tiedown Controls, Original File Number 38.E (Box 72, Folder 45)
        - B4 Forms, Original File Number 38.F (Box 73, Folder 1)
        - Tiedown Drives, Original File Number 38.G (Box 73, Folder 2)
        - Jacks, Original File Number 38.H (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Towers
        - Steel Tower Concepts RSI, Original File Number 39.A (Box 73, Folder 4)
        - Tower Banding, Original File Number 39.B (Box 73, Folder 5)
        - T4, Original File Number 39.C (Box 73, Folder 6)
        - T8, Original File Number 39.D (Box 73, Folder 7)
        - T12, Original File Number 39.E (Box 73, Folder 8)
        - Tower Installation General, Original File Number 39.F (Box 73, Folder 9)
        - General, Original File Number 39.G (Box 73, Folder 10)
        - Tower Crane, Original File Number 39.H (Box 73, Folder 11)
        - T8 Hoist, Original File Number 39.I (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Waveguide and Weight Management
        - 430 MHz System, Original File Number 40.A (Box 73, Folder 13)
        - Waveguide Calcs - General, Original File Number 40.B (Box 73, Folder 14)
        - Weight Management, Original File Number 41.A (Box 73, Folder 15)
        - Dome, Original File Number 41.B (Box 73, Folder 16)
        - Platform Weight, Original File Number 41.C (Box 73, Folder 17)
      - Welds & Testing and Welder Qualifications/Mill Certs
        - West Testing (UT), Original File Number 42.A (Box 73, Folder 18)
        - Inspection & Repairs, Original File Number 42.B (Box 73, Folder 19)
        - Welding, Original File Number 42.C (Box 73, Folder 20)
        - Welder Qualifications, Original File Number 43.A (Box 73, Folder 21)
        - Struct Steels - Raw Mater Certs, Original File Number 43.B (Box 73, Folder 22)
        - Anchor Bolt Test Report (C of C), Original File Number 43.C (Box 73, Folder 23)
        - Concrete 3000/4000 PSI, Original File Number 43.D (Box 73, Folder 24)
        - Cable C of Cs (1), Original File Number 43.E (Box 73, Folder 25)
        - Cable C of Cs (2), Original File Number 43.E (Box 73, Folder 26)
        - Cable C of Cs (3), Original File Number 43.E (Box 73, Folder 27)
- Series V. Publications
  - Manuals
    - NAIC Manuals, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - NAIC Manuals, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - User's Manual, 1976-1978 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Reprints
    - Reprint Series 1-76 (Box 16)
    - Reprint Series 77-205 (Box 17)
    - Reprint Series 206-317 (Box 18)
    - Reprint Series 318-449 (Box 19)
  - News Articles
    - "Large Antennas, Cornell 1000ft Dish" (R.C. Hansen), 1961 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Engineering News Record - "Radio Telescope Sight Trouble", 7/6/1961 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - "Slip Forms Used on World's Largest Radar", 10/20/1961 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Engineering News Record - "1000-Ft Telescope Takes Shape in Mountain Hollow" (Thomas C. Kavanagh), 1/10/1963 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Aviation Week & Space Technology - "New Radar Telescope to Map Ionosphere" (Philip J. Klass), 8/19/1963 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Cornell Alumni News - "Big ear at Arecibo" (Thomas Tobin), Dec-63 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Vision - "Un ojo de 300 metros", 4/3/1964 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Visão - "Arecibo conversa com os astros", 4/24/1964 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Fortune - "Space Explorers Build Their Dream Telescope", Aug-64 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Sky & Telescope - "Some Current Programs at Arecibo" (Charles A. Federer Jr.), Jul/Aug-64 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Science - "Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory - Studies of the upper atmosphere and planets are made with the aid of a huge reflector in Puerto Rico" (William E. Gordon), 10/2/1964 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Iberica Actualidad Cientifica - "Las Primeras Observaciones de Arecibo" (Pascual Bolufer, S.I.), Jan-65 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - The New York Times - "Radar Observations Show Mercury is Rotating and Mars has a Flat Spot" (Evert Clark), 4/21/1965 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Journal of the Construction Division - "Arecibo Radar-Radio Telescope -- Design and Construction" (Thomas C. Kavangh & David H.H. Tung), May-65 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - The New York Times - "Huge Radio Telescope in Puerto Rico Gathers Data on Mysterious Quasars" (Walter Sullivan), 1/30/1966 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - The New York Times - "Astronomers Hear Signals from Space" (Walter Sullivan), 3/10/1968 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Life - "Signals from a Quadrillion Miles" (John J. Fried), 5/3/1968 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - AP News Features - "The Big Ear", 5/25/1968 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Central Bureau for Astronomical Telegrams - "New Pulsar, AP2015+28" (Brian G. Marsden), 8/30/1968 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - CRSR - Publication and information policies for the AO (T. Gold), 11/18/1969 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - The Science World - "Arecibo: a radio telescope in limbo", 8/18/1969 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Cornell Chronicle - "Cornell Scientists Find Lunar Rock Chemically Homogeneous", 1/8/1970 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Cornell University News - "Addition of Extendable Boom" (Ralph Kazarian), 2/12/1970 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Nature - "More Delay at Arecibo", 4/25/1970 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Cornell University News - "Team of French Astronomers visit the Arecibo Observatory" (Ralph Kazarian), 6/23/1970 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - El Mundo - "Observatorio Arecibo Estudia Ionosfera", 9/23/1970 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - NSF News - "Cyanoacetylene, A New Stage of Molecular Complexity, Found in Interstellar Space" (William Howard), 10/4/1970 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Cornell University News - "85-ft spherical radio telescope being constructed at Danby lab" (Ralph Kazarian), 10/7/1970 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Cornell University News - "Upgrading of Arecibo Observatory will start next fall" (Ralph Kazarian), 4/23/1971 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Cornell University News - "Observatory name change to National Astronomy & Ionosphere Center" (Ralph Kazarian), 6/2/1971 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Cornell University News - "Martin Harwit named Chair of Astronomy Dept" (Ralph Kazarian), 9/7/1971 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Cornell University News - "Yervant Terzian promoted to Associate Profesor", 11/9/1971 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Cornell University News - "Cornell has awarded contract to LTV Electrosystems for upgrade of telescope" (Ralph Kazarian), 11/29/1971 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - The Sciences - "Short Takes - The World's largest radio-radar telescope will undergo a non-cosmetic face-left…", Dec-71 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Cornell University News - "First spacecraft to leave solar system - Pioneer 10" (Ralph Kazarian), 2/25/1972 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Cornell University News - "New power line feed at Arecibo Observatory" (Ralph Kazarian), 3/15/1972 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - "The National Astronomy and Ionosphere Center" (Yervant Terzian), Apr-72 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Cornell Alumni News - "Talking to the Stars", May-72 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Cornell University News - "Saturn suitable for life like that on Earth" (Ralph Kazarian), 5/2/1972 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Cornell University News - "Radar Triple Bounce Between Earth & Moon" (Ralph Kazarian), 5/10/1972 (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Sky & Telescope - "Arecibo Observatory Today - II" (William E. Shawcross), 5/15/1972 (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Cornell Chronicle - "Research Team to View Eclipse, Do Experiments", 6/6/1972 (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Science Saturday Review - "Search for Man's Relatives Among the Stars" (John Lear), 6/10/1972 (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Science News - "Modernizing Arecibo's 1000-ft Dish" (Kendrick Frazier), 12/30/1972 (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - The New York Times - "Largest Radio Telescope", 6/3/1973 (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Cornell Chronicle - "Tenth Birthday for Arecibo", 11/1/1973 (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Cornell University News - Board of Trustees approve improvements to Arecibo, 11/16/1973 (Box 53, Folder 46.1)
    - International Literary Report - "1973 Marks the 10th Anniversary of Arecibo, 11/30/1973 (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Cincinnati Enquirer - "SuperBowl", 12/28/1973 (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Cleveland Press - "Largest radio telescope getrs aluminum surface", 2/7/1974 (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Science News - "Arecibo Reborn", Aug 24 & 31, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - Cornell University News - "1974 Dedication of Upgraded Arecibo" (Dava Sobel), 10/11/1974 (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Science - The Upgraded Arecibo Observatory (L.M. LaLonde), 10/18/1974 (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - The Dallas Morning News - "Telephone to Outer Space - E-Systems Revamps Research Telescope" (David Clark), 10/20/1974 (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - El Dairio La Prensa - "Escrutando el Cielo Desde Arecibo, El Radio Telescopio Mas Grande del Mundo Esta en P.R., 10/20/1974 (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Que Pasa - Official Visitors Guide to Puerto Rico, Nov-74 (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Puerto Rico Illustrado - "Un Ojo Observando el Universo", 11/10/1974 (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - Washington Post - "Beam Sent to Find Other Civilization", 11/17/1974 (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - Cornell Chronicle - "New Radio Telescope - A Greeting from Arecibo Speeds to the Stars" (Dava Sobel), 11/21/1974 (Box 53, Folder 58)
    - Science News - "Hello", said earth. "Is anybody there?", 11/23/1974 (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - The Oregonian - "Long wait likely" (Jay Ellis Ransom), 11/23/1974 (Box 53, Folder 60)
    - NSF MOSAIC - "Extending Man's Reach", Fall 1974 (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - Arecibo brochure "A Time of Wonder", 1974 (Box 53, Folder 62)
    - The Arts College Observer - "Astronomy: How complex is the universe?", Nov-74 (Box 53, Folder 63)
    - San Juan Star - "Arecibo dish serves up a complex space menu" (Walter Sullivan), 11/24/1974 (Box 53, Folder 64)
    - Newsweek - "The Big Dish", 11/25/1974 (Box 53, Folder 65)
    - Ithaca Journal - "Is Pulsating Star Survivor of an Earlier Universe?" (Thomas O'Toole), 11/25/1974 (Box 53, Folder 66)
    - Ithaca Journal - "A Message Out There…" (Dava Sobel), 11/27/1974 (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - The Atlanta Journal - "Earth to Stars: 'Anybody There?'", Nov-74 (Box 53, Folder 68)
    - Ithaca New Times - "Space Letter: To Whom (or What) It May Concern" (Dava Sobel), 12/15/1974 (Box 53, Folder 69)
    - Die Zeit - "Bildpost an die Geschwister im All" (Von Peter Fischer), 12/13/1974 (Box 53, Folder 70)
    - Cornell Alumni News - "Tuning the Big Ear", Dec-74 (Box 53, Folder 71)
    - Engineering Cornell Quarterly - "Upgrading the Arecibo Observatory", 12/30/1974 (Box 53, Folder 72)
    - Experimental Mechanics - "Dedication of Arecibo Observatory", Jan-75 (Box 53, Folder 73)
    - "Arecibo Message Received" (Ed Fomalont), Apr-75 (Box 53, Folder 74)
    - Science Trends - Arecibo Dedication, 4/28/1975 (Box 53, Folder 75)
    - Adler Planetarium Newsletter - "Far out message", Spring 1975 (Box 53, Folder 76)
    - Probe - "First Halting Steps Toward Interstellar Contact" (Robert B. Klinn), 1975 (Box 53, Folder 77)
    - "Misschien Lomt de Redding Wel Van Boven" (Jan Willem Clinge Doorenbos), 1975 (Box 53, Folder 78)
    - The Sciences - "Reflections in an Aluminum Ear" (James Gorman), May/June 1975 (Box 53, Folder 79)
    - NY Sunday News - "Eye on the Universe" (Edward Edelson), 3/2/1975 (Box 53, Folder 80)
    - Contact for Control Data People - Cover with photos of Arecibo, June/July 1975 (Box 53, Folder 81)
    - Harvard Magazine - "Reaching across space" (Dava Sobel), Dec-75 (Box 53, Folder 82)
    - St. Louis Post - "World's Without End" (Jim Creighton), 6/27/1976 (Box 53, Folder 83)
    - San Juan Star - "From Arecibo…To Mars…And Beyond…" (Bob McCoy), 6/28/1976 (Box 53, Folder 84)
    - St. Louis Post-Dispatch - "A Long Way Between Calls" (Jim Creighton), 6/28/1976 (Box 53, Folder 85)
    - St. Louis Post-Dispatch - "Broadening the Search" (Jim Creighton), 6/29/1976 (Box 53, Folder 86)
    - St. Louis Post-Dispatch - "Communication with Alien Life" (Jim Creighton), 7/1/1976 (Box 53, Folder 87)
    - National Geographic - "Who's Out There?", Sep-76 (Box 53, Folder 88)
    - Cornell University News - First detailed radar pictures of Venus, 9/10/1976 (Box 53, Folder 89)
    - Ithaca Journal - "Arecibo pictures of Venus show Lava flow as big as Oklahoma", 9/10/1976 (Box 53, Folder 90)
    - New York Times - "Radar Images from Venus Depict Vast Area of Possible Lava Flow" (John Noble Wilford), 9/10/1976 (Box 53, Folder 91)
    - NY Times Magazine - "Is Anybody Out There?" (Tom Buckley), 9/12/1976 (Box 53, Folder 92)
    - Cornell Chronicle - "Venus Pictures Hint of Earth-Like Processes", 9/16/1976 (Box 53, Folder 93)
    - AP-S Newsletter - "Arecibo Radio Antenna", Oct-76 (Box 53, Folder 94)
    - McGraw Hill Yearbook - "Radio Telescope", 1976 (Box 53, Folder 95)
    - "Tudomanyos osszefogas", 1976 (Box 53, Folder 96)
    - Ithaca Journal - "Searching for extraterrestrial life" (Philip Nobile), 12/22/76 (Box 53, Folder 97)
    - Cornell Chronicle - "Paradise it isn't" (Connie Bart), 3/24/1977 (Box 53, Folder 98)
    - MOSAIC - "Life Among the Stars", March/April 1977 (Box 53, Folder 99)
    - Syracuse Herald American - "'Dish' will reveal secrets of Venus", 4/24/1977 (Box 53, Folder 100)
    - "Unveiling Venus", May-77 (Box 53, Folder 101)
    - Continental Electronics brochure - "Mapping the Universe", May-77 (Box 53, Folder 102)
    - Cornell University News - Dale Corson appointed Chancellor of Cornell, 5/30/1977 (Box 53, Folder 103)
    - Accessibility of NAIC facilities to the media, 8/16/1977 (Box 53, Folder 104)
    - San Juan Star - "Hello, out there" (Jorge A. Colon Catano), 8/10/1977 (Box 53, Folder 105)
    - "Desde aqui, el hombre se quiere comunicar con otras galaxies", 1977 (Box 53, Folder 106)
    - Newsweek - "Seeking Other Worlds"-Carl Sagan, 8-15-77 (Box 53, Folder 107)
    - Canadian Communications Quarterly - "The search for extraterrestrial intelligence" (John Sifton), Mar-78 (Box 53, Folder 108)
    - Cornell Chronicle - "Star light, star bright, first star I hear tonight", 4/10/1978 (Box 53, Folder 109)
    - Smithsonian Institute - "Searching for Intelligent Life in Space" (Carl Sagan), May-78 (Box 53, Folder 110)
    - Morning Advocate - "World's Largest Radio Telescope Causes Problems" (George Alexander), 5/18/1978 (Box 53, Folder 111)
    - Modern Electronics - "Arecibo: the quest for knowledge" (Dava Sobel), Jul-78 (Box 53, Folder 112)
    - Amateur Radio - "Chasing the Ultimate DX" (Paul Horowitz), Dec-78 (Box 53, Folder 113)
    - Cornell University News - Radar pictures of Venus show wide variety of terrains, 4/24/1979 (Box 53, Folder 114)
    - Journal of British Interplanetary Society - "The Arecibo Observatory", 1979 (Box 53, Folder 115)
    - MOSAIC - "the Great Astronomical Ear", Mar/Apr 1980 (Box 53, Folder 116)
    - Gentlemen's Quarterly - "American Know-How: Technology that's paving the way to the future" (Peter Carlsen), Aug-80 (Box 53, Folder 117)
    - Cornell University News - Thomas Gold's 60th Birthday celebration, 9/16/1980 (Box 53, Folder 118)
    - Amator Radio - "Arecibo-Antennen" (Roald Steen), Nov-80 (Box 53, Folder 119)
    - Science News - "Reagan Axes Science Budget", 3/14/1981 (Box 53, Folder 120)
    - MPG Spiegel - "SOUSY sucht nach tropischen Wellen", Mar-81 (Box 53, Folder 121)
    - American Astronomical Society Newsletter - "NSF Astronomy Faces $2M cut this year", Apr-81 (Box 53, Folder 122)
    - Cornell University News - Martin Harwit's book "Cosmic Discovery", 6/19/1981 (Box 53, Folder 123)
    - Cornell University News - Hal Craft named Acting Director of NAIC, 7/27/1981 (Box 53, Folder 124)
    - Wall Street Journal - "The Budget Cuts: Picking What Works and What Doesn't", 9/25/1981 (Box 53, Folder 125)
    - Hong Kong Space Museum brochure - Radio Telescopes, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 126)
    - Esquire - "The Ears of the Earth" (David Noonan), Apr-82 (Box 53, Folder 127)
    - NSF News - "Astronomers discover pulsar that rotates more than 600 times per second" (Ralph Kazarian), Nov-82 (Box 53, Folder 128)
    - Edmond Evening Sun - "Astronomers Reveal Discovery of Vast String of Galaxies", 11/30/1982 (Box 53, Folder 129)
    - Ithaca Journal - "Astronomers discover huge string of galaxies", 11/30/1982 (Box 53, Folder 130)
    - NSF News - "Largest known structure in universe id identified by two astronomers" (Ralph Kazarian), 11/30/1982 (Box 53, Folder 131)
    - USA Today - "A real search for real E.T. We listen for talk from 1,000 stars" (Michael W. Fincham), 12/6/1982 (Box 53, Folder 132)
    - Cornell University News - Elongated interfalactic hydrogen gas cloud discovered, 2/25/1983 (Box 53, Folder 133)
    - Ithaca Journal - "Search for life in space: We will make contact" (Lee Scott), 3/23/1983 (Box 53, Folder 134)
    - Cornell University News - First fast-rotating pulsar discovered, 5/20/1983 (Box 53, Folder 135)
    - El Nuevo Dia - "Reagan le dio la notica a Lafitte", 5/26/1983 (Box 53, Folder 136)
    - Ithaca Journal - "Astronmer sets his sights on a whirling star" (Helen Mundell), 6/15/1983 (Box 53, Folder 137)
    - Cornell Chronicle - "Arecibo Scientists Mark 20th Year", 11/1/1983 (Box 53, Folder 138)
    - "Arecibo -- radar, receiver, transmitter" (Kerry Manos), 1983 (Box 53, Folder 139)
    - Capitol - "The Biggest Dish in the World" (Seth Shostak), 1984-85? (Box 53, Folder 140)